Hello and welcome to the insurance world, everyone.
Today, we're going to suggest five of the best personal
accident insurance plans
and share their details.
You can choose your plan as per your convenience.
But before that, if you
want to buy any insurance plan, you
can click on the link given in the description box and get a hassle-free, stress-
free insurance plan. Let's
start the video. What is personal accident
insurance? Basically, an
accident insurance plan provides you with money
if you suffer a loss in an accident.
This plan can help you
in difficult times of injury and permanent disability.
If the
person in question, i.e., the policyholder,
dies due to an accident, the sum is
given to the nominee in short. The first
name is the Star Health Accident Policy.
This is an individual and family floater policy
that covers dependent children from 5 months and
adults between the ages of 18 and 70.
Dangers covered under the Star Health Accident Policy  Such as accidental death, permanent
total disability, permanent partial
disability, temporary total disability and
many more. You
also get some extra benefits under this policy without
any additional premium such as education
grants, ambulance charges for children,
hospital cash. It has a minimum sum
assured amount of Rs 1 lakh and there is no maximum
limit. The second best personal
accident insurance plan is Niva Bupa
Accident Care Plan. Niva Bupa Personal
Accident Care is a plan that
covers you against various accident-related risks.
This plan includes
accidental death, permanent total disability,
permanent partial disability, child
education benefit and coverage of funeral expenses.
Sum assured options are Rs 5 lakh to Rs 25
lakh and Rs 30 lakh to Rs 5 crore. Minimum entry
age is 18 years and maximum is 65 years. This
plan offers you both individual and family floater insurance.  The
third best
personal accident insurance is SBI
Personal Accident Insurance. This policy
can be purchased by those above 18 years of age.
You can buy this policy for your spouse, parents, and in-
law children. This plan
also covers accidental death, permanent total disability, permanent partial disability, and temporary total disability. The
sum assured in this plan ranges from Rs. 1 lakh to Rs. 1
crore. The policy term is one year and the
initial waiting period is 30 days.
You
also get tax benefits and added covers in SBI Personal Accident Insurance. The
child entry age for this plan is 3
months to 20 years and for adults, it is 18
to 65 years. The fourth best plan is Care
Secure Personal Accident Insurance. Care
Plan Care Secure Personal Accident
Policy covers you against accidental death, permanent and
temporary partial total disability, recovery,
treatment due to accidental burns, fracture, motor,
remaining mobility, and more.  A lot
is included in this
policy. Another advantage of this policy is its
lifelong renewability benefit, which
guarantees your children a brighter future.
If the insured individual
dies in an accident or suffers
permanent total disability, making it
impossible for them to care for their children's education, this policy
provides educational support to the children. The
child entry age for this plan is 91 days
to 24 years, and the adult entry age is 18 to
70 years. You will get sum insured options ranging from ₹10 lakh to ₹
50 lakh. Last
on the list of plans is the Aditya Billa Active
Secure Personal Accident Policy, which
provides coverage to the insured individual: 100%
cover for permanent disabilities due to
accidents, 100% cover on accidental death, and
income cover during temporary total
disability due to accidents.
To customize this plan, follow three easy
steps.  In the first step,
you select your base sum assured,
which can range from ₹1 lakh to ₹20 crore. The
second step involves choosing the base coverage for customers.
Five different
base plans are available, each with different
features and benefits. In the third step,
you select any of the plan's 11 optional covers.
These 11 optional covers are: Temporary
Total Disability Insurance, Accident Inpatient
Hospitalization Cover, MI Protect, Broker
Bonus Benefit, Loan Protect, Coma Benefit,
Burn Benefit, Accidental Medical
Expenses, Adventure Sports Cover,
Worldwide Emergency Assistance Services, and
Wonless Coach Entry. The minimum age for this plan
is five years and the maximum is
65 years. These were the best personal
accident insurance plans. If you
want a detailed review of any plan, don't leave any
comment below. To
buy any health or term plan,
click on the link below. Until then, bye, take
care and  Happy Inshore